And. You do not no matter.
What your name Gambit or your
occupation. I'm allowed to do it or
you working in
a black bottom can be when this murder was
committed yes but I didn't do it then
the rule Rob one I don't know do
you live forever and ask for the
last question be stricken from the record
it is merely an attempt to influence an
intelligent broad minded and
most intellectual jury.
Objection sustained Thank you
Your Honor. That you know.
Why. It would please the court Your Honor
at this time I would like to introduce my
three main witnesses
Howard Fine and Howard.
They were here
a minute ago when you pardon me
your honor I'll be right back. OK
.
OK but the idea is born again i wish
me well here's. A warning you getting
hit by. A gentleman home don't
you realize risking your campus
life for the sake. Of.
You General Ban we use try to be
a little more quiet on the court. Of
law will you please step forward.
No no no prepare yourself
for the witness box.
Take over at. Our you're right an
operator and here they go you're ad.
Radio right man but you're
going to end here. We've got
a lawyer had. Raise your
right. Now put your hand here
when you leave paid off
you are had. Your rights
in. Our journey here you're. Right you're
right man we get for that
matter. Right your right Nancy.
Raise your right hand you tell me for
example go do that I'm going to do. You son
of the president who told you that I'm
going to do I don't mean the photo are.
Doing how many friends
who don't could have
a clue why don't you
answer him. Nobody thank.
You if you know where you are but I know
why. You are you will swear to tell the
truth who can stand you thank
you get you when he. Finally
addressed this court as Your Honor and take
the old. You tell him you spread it out
who don't do that out of the to me when I
got an early thank the staff. Were not.
No No OK I am. What I do it.
Going to point to plenty more
room. Than. What you are getting.
Right. To say you know the case.
Where you want a black
Andrea one hundred you were
a thirty eight. Did you at that time see
the defendant Mr Gale tempest in any way
shape or form commit or try to commit bodily
harm to the deceased or grabbing your
own I don't really do
it day to day. But hour
did you see Mr Gale tempest in physical
fight with her Robin I believe because I
suggested
a counselor be instructed to allow the
witness to testify to what he saw. I think
yes but what can that upset
me. I let me make this very.
Request. Proceed with the testimony
Mr Howard finally got or what your
current one of the latest addressed the
charges Your Honor what I would like is my
honor your honor not my honor why
don't you like. The witness to
proceed with court orders things you
think or your. Well me in my hands
when you say humans we want to know sometimes
when you think you are gay or when
they wish when the man as Sweet could Robin
within hail the battle who get cable
and hope by the name of wing will get
ready to hear you concede. Kindly speak
English and drop the burning or. Thank
you let. Me drop the Burnett you are.
To know that talk so the jury can understand
if everybody thank you again if you
let me my partner and get any kind of it
out for you we will show you just what
happened and come from the object
that I met on the night in a dark
a North Koreans no objection. OK me.
Friend.
You.
Are. Right good luck.
To you. More simplistic to say oh my thank
you gentlemen you must control your I
mean you. Perceive in the past I mean you.
You have no.
Free.
Wait
a minute the rest of the entertainment and
continue. Now gaily dance was over I stuck
my head in the office door and I saw quite
prominent borrowing argument I want
a parrot cage for an army of Iran are all
but bubbling with the one I am I have
a graphic I can make my campaign
and bank I'm going to have
a price range. I. Think Mike
and I had like. Anybody
come out into the lot of pressure saying
my dad and he said. That right here Adam's
apple let me get in the way try to.
Get it.
You What You Want you me by the bar whatever
you are going to be all they are going
to get bending over the fire the murdered
man want to rape. But you're only going
to prove that my client it exactly and I
mean ladies and gentlemen the action of
this hard work a good friend
to whom you may want to pull
a trigger. For. Iran to join. Some of you
who are. Member of your if not noted.
How could be your papers write you
a little bigger pull the rescue trigger of
that instrument of destruction. The one
that.
Broadly ninety nine you can. Get by on.
What you do in my book.
They are boy what part of you
would what you would you know be
a button in your support of the I want
to hear what they mean and what in the
spinal cord for. Me.
But. Me.
Come away. Look again.
But I'm an old I'll get.
A point I want to cause man. Are in
accord.
With Our me by. I find the
letter so prevalent today.
That I don't talk to the parents but. I
bring them up on my body come up money buy
by me come on.
My. Period come on.
How we get mileage you. Know when I get
got to when it's my duty you know for
me and I'm. Waiting all the.
Way I.
Got.
At it. And I
want to. We.
Got a second.